Guide to the Nasri Fuleihan Collection AD.MC.056
Akkasah: Photography Archive (NYU Abu Dhabi)
- Nasri Fuleihan Collection
  - The Cyclopean Wall, Baalbek., Circa 1910s - 1930s; ref96; Fuleihan, Nasri Suleiman; 1 Photographic Prints; 11.4 x 7.9 com (Object 056 Digital Copy Only)
    Baalbek, Lebanon; Gelatin Silver Prints; Photographic Prints; English Writing; Archaeological Sites/Artifacts; Buildings
  - People walking downhill near a building., Circa 1910s - 1930s; ref97; Fuleihan, Nasri Suleiman; 1 Photographic Prints; 8.4 x 11 cm (Object 056 Digital Copy Only)
    Buildings; Palm Trees; Mountains/Hills; Landscapes; Men; Women; Canes/Walking Sticks; Group Portraits; Gelatin Silver Prints; Photographic Prints; Palestine; Hats
  - A man on a horse in front of a stone wall., Circa 1910s - 1930s; ref98; Fuleihan, Nasri Suleiman; 1 Photographic Prints; 14 x 8.5 cm (Object 056 Digital Copy Only)
    Horses; Men; Individual Portraits; Animals; Regional/National Dress; Photographic Prints; Gelatin Silver Prints; Palestine
  - The Inn of the Good Samaritan, Khan Al-Ahmar., Circa 1910s - 1930s; ref99; Fuleihan, Nasri Suleiman; 1 Photographic Prints; 11.4 x 8.4 cm (Object 056 Digital Copy Only)
    English Writing; Streets/Roads; Mountains/Hills; Photographic Prints; Gelatin Silver Prints; Palestine; Landscapes
  - An aerial view of a village., Circa 1910s - 1930s; ref100; Fuleihan, Nasri Suleiman; 1 Photographic Prints; 8.4 x 13.9 cm (Object 056 Digital Copy Only)
    Buildings; Landscapes; Streets/Roads; Palestine; Gelatin Silver Prints; Photographic Prints
  - Man standing in front of Samson's Cave, Palestine., Circa 1910s - 1930s; ref101; Fuleihan, Nasri Suleiman; 1 Photographic Prints; 11.4 x 8.4 cm (Object 056 Digital Copy Only)
    Men; Caves; Archaeological Sites/Artifacts; Religious Sites; Palestine; Individual Portraits; Gelatin Silver Prints; Photographic Prints; English Writing
  - Bedouin camp near Asluj., Circa 1910s - 1930s; ref102; Fuleihan, Nasri Suleiman; 1 Photographic Prints; 8.3 x 14.4 cm (Object 056 Digital Copy Only)
    Dogs; Tents; Animals; Women; Individual Portraits; Deserts; Palestine; Photographic Prints; Gelatin Silver Prints; English Writing; Bir 'Asluj
  - Group portrait men and women in a wadi., Circa 1910s - 1930s; ref103; Fuleihan, Nasri Suleiman; 1 Photographic Prints; 8.3 x 11.2 cm (Object 056 Digital Copy Only)
    Men; Women; Hats; Group Portraits; Palestine; Water; Photographic Prints; Gelatin Silver Prints
  - Group portrait of men on a rooftop., Circa 1910s - 1930s; ref104; Fuleihan, Nasri Suleiman; 1 Photographic Prints; 8.2 x 14 cm (Object 056 Digital Copy Only)
    Men; Regional/National Dress; Swords/Knives; Weapons; Group Portraits; Palestine; Photographic Prints; Gelatin Silver Prints; Facial Hair
  - Acacia tree at Ein Gedi, Dead Sea., Circa 1910s - 1930s; ref105; Fuleihan, Nasri Suleiman; 1 Photographic Prints; 8.2 x 14.5 cm (Object 056 Digital Copy Only)
    Landscapes; Dead Sea; Water; Photographic Prints; Gelatin Silver Prints; English Writing; Palestine
  - Tents and construction supplies., Circa 1910s - 1930s; ref106; Fuleihan, Nasri Suleiman; 1 Photographic Prints; 8.3 x 13.9 cm (Object 056 Digital Copy Only)
    Tents; Construction; Photographic Prints; Gelatin Silver Prints; Palestine; Deserts
  - Camp near the Dead Sea., Circa 1910s - 1930s; ref107; Fuleihan, Nasri Suleiman; 1 Photographic Prints; 8.3 x 14.6 x cm (Object 056 Digital Copy Only)
    Water; Dead Sea; Mountains/Hills; Boats/Ships; Transportation; Tents; Cars/Trucks; Buildings; Photographic Prints; Gelatin Silver Prints; English Writing; Palestine; Landscapes
  - Women and a girl grinding wheat in front of a stone building., Circa 1910s - 1930s; ref108; Fuleihan, Nasri Suleiman; 1 Photographic Prints; 11.5 x 8.6 cm (Object 056 Digital Copy Only)
    Women; Girls; Children; Workers; Group Portraits; Regional/National Dress; Embroidery; Head Covers/Veils; Photographic Prints; Gelatin Silver Prints; Palestine; English Writing
  - Men standing on a balcony overlooking machinery (linked ref18)., Circa 1910s - 1930s; ref109; Fuleihan, Nasri Suleiman; 1 Photographic Prints; 12.5 x 9.2 cm (Object 056 Digital Copy Only)
    Machines; Men; Group Portraits; Hats; North America; Photographic Prints; Gelatin Silver Prints
  - The House of the Sheikh, Bayt Nattif., Circa 1910s - 1930s; ref110; Fuleihan, Nasri Suleiman; 1 Photographic Prints; 8.3 x 14.5 cm (Object 056 Digital Copy Only)
    Sheep; Houses; Buildings; Men; Palestine; Individual Portraits; Animals; Photographic Prints; Gelatin Silver Prints; English Writing; Bayt Nattif
  - Vertical view from bottom of Wadi Mujib, Jordan., Circa 1910s - 1930s; ref111; Fuleihan, Nasri Suleiman; 1 Photographic Prints; 14.5 x 8.3 cm (Object 056 Digital Copy Only)
    Ma'in, Jordan; English Writing; Outdoors; Photographic Prints; Gelatin Silver Prints
  - Cliff on the west side of Ein Gedi, Dead Sea., Circa 1910s - 1930s; ref112; Fuleihan, Nasri Suleiman; 1 Photographic Prints; 8.4 x 14.8 cm (Object 056 Digital Copy Only)
    Mountains/Hills; Dead Sea; Landscapes; English Writing; Photographic Prints; Gelatin Silver Prints; Ain Jidi/Ein Gedi; Palestine
  - River flow through Wadi Mujib, Dead Sea Jordan., Circa 1910s - 1930s; ref113; Fuleihan, Nasri Suleiman; 1 Photographic Prints; 14.5 x 8.3 cm (Object 056 Digital Copy Only)
    Rivers; Water; English Writing; Ma'in, Jordan; Dead Sea; Photographic Prints; Gelatin Silver Prints; Landscapes
  - Cliffs on the west side of Ein Gedi, Dead Sea., Circa 1910s - 1930s; ref114; Fuleihan, Nasri Suleiman; 1 Photographic Prints; 8.3 x 14.5 cm (Object 056 Digital Copy Only)
    Mountains/Hills; Water; Dead Sea; Landscapes; English Writing; Photographic Prints; Gelatin Silver Prints; Ain Jidi/Ein Gedi; Palestine
  - Man standing in front of rock formation., Circa 1910s - 1930s; ref115; Fuleihan, Nasri Suleiman; 1 Photographic Prints; 8.8 x 6.5 cm (Object 056 Digital Copy Only)
    Men; Smoking; Hats; Palestine; Individual Portraits; Outdoors; Photographic Prints; Gelatin Silver Prints; Tobacco pipes
  - A campsite., Circa 1910s - 1930s; ref116; Fuleihan, Nasri Suleiman; 1 Photographic Prints; 6.5 x 8.8 cm (Object 056 Digital Copy Only)
    Tents; Palestine; Photographic Prints; Gelatin Silver Prints; Countryside/Rural; Landscapes
  - A person next to a herd of sheep and camels., Circa 1910s - 1930s; ref117; Fuleihan, Nasri Suleiman; 1 Photographic Prints; 6.5 x 8.9 cm (Object 056 Digital Copy Only)
    Sheep; Camels; Animals; Men; Individual Portraits; Photographic Prints; Gelatin Silver Prints; Palestine
  - Nasri Fuleihan holding a gun., Circa 1910s - 1930s; ref118; Fuleihan, Nasri Suleiman; 1 Photographic Prints; 8.4 x 6 cm (Object 056 Digital Copy Only)
    Guns; Weapons; Men; Facial Hair; Photographic Prints; Gelatin Silver Prints; Individual Portraits; Palestine
  - A river flowing between rock formations., Circa 1910s - 1930s; ref119; Fuleihan, Nasri Suleiman; 1 Photographic Prints; 12.9 x 8.4 cm (Object 056 Digital Copy Only)
    Water; Photographic Prints; Gelatin Silver Prints; Palestine; Landscapes; Rivers
  - People standing in front of Herod's Gate, Jerusalem., Circa 1910s - 1930s; ref120; Fuleihan, Nasri Suleiman; 1 Photographic Prints; 11.3 x 8.5 cm (Object 056 Digital Copy Only)
    English Writing; Doors/Entrances; Photographic Prints; Gelatin Silver Prints; Men; Women; Children; Boys; Head Covers/Veils; Streets/Roads; Donkeys; Animals; Jerusalem; Palestine
  - Landscape of Ein Gedi, Dead Sea., Circa 1910s - 1930s; ref122; Fuleihan, Nasri Suleiman; 1 Photographic Prints; 8.2 x 14 cm (Object 056 Digital Copy Only)
    Mountains/Hills; Water; Dead Sea; Photographic Prints; Landscapes; English Writing; Gelatin Silver Prints; Ain Jidi/Ein Gedi; Palestine
  - A mountainous landscape, Dead Sea., Circa 1910s - 1930s; ref123; Fuleihan, Nasri Suleiman; 1 Photographic Prints; 8.4 x 14.5 cm (Object 056 Digital Copy Only)
    English Writing; Dead Sea; Mountains/Hills; Gelatin Silver Prints; Photographic Prints; Landscapes; Water; Palestine
  - Man standing in front of a mountain range, Kerak, Jordan., Circa 1910s - 1930s; ref124; Fuleihan, Nasri Suleiman; 1 Photographic Prints; 8.3 x 14.3 cm (Object 056 Digital Copy Only)
    Mountains/Hills; Hats; Men; Landscapes; Individual Portraits; Photographic Prints; Gelatin Silver Prints; Kerak, Jordan; English Writing
  - Cliffs and a body of water north of Wadi Zarqa Ma'in, Jordan., Circa 1910s - 1930s; ref125; Fuleihan, Nasri Suleiman; 1 Photographic Prints; 14.2 x 8.5 cm (Object 056 Digital Copy Only)
    Water; Ma'in, Jordan; Mountains/Hills; Photographic Prints; Gelatin Silver Prints; English Writing; Landscapes
  - East cliffs of Dead Sea, North of Wadi Zarqa Ma'in, Jordan., Circa 1910s - 1930s; ref126; Fuleihan, Nasri Suleiman; 1 Photographic Prints; 8.4 x 14.6 cm (Object 056 Digital Copy Only)
    Water; Dead Sea; Mountains/Hills; Gelatin Silver Prints; Landscapes; Photographic Prints; English Writing; Ma'in, Jordan
  - The White Mosque (tower of Forty Martyrs), Ramla., Circa 1910s - 1930s; ref127; Fuleihan, Nasri Suleiman; 1 Photographic Prints; 11.3 x 8.5 cm (Object 056 Digital Copy Only)
    Ramla/ar-Ramlah; White Mosque, Ramla; Mosques; Religious Sites; Architecture; Men; Fez/Tarboush; Individual Portraits; Photographic Prints; Gelatin Silver Prints; English Writing; Palestine; Hats
  - Two men and a woman standing in the Ashkelon/Ashqelon archeological site. (linked refs 142, 143, 367 and 415)., Circa 1923 - 1930; ref128; Fuleihan, Nasri Suleiman; 1 Photographic Prints; 10.3 X 7.9 cm (Object 056 Digital Copy Only)
    Men; Women; Archaeological Sites/Artifacts; Hats; Palestine; Group Portraits; Bow Ties; Photographic Prints; Gelatin Silver Prints; Statues/Sculptures; Ashḳelon/Ashqelon; Group Portraits
  - Chapel of Saint Helena, Jerusalem., Circa 1910s - 1930s; ref129; Fuleihan, Nasri Suleiman; 1 Photographic Prints; 8.6 X 11.3 cm (Object 056 Digital Copy Only)
    Chandeliers; Furnishings; Art; Photographic Prints; Gelatin Silver Prints; Religious Sites; English Writing; Church of the Holy Sepulchre; Jerusalem; Palestine; Churches; Archaeological Sites/Artifacts
  - Landscape of rock formation., Circa 1910s - 1930s; ref130; Fuleihan, Nasri Suleiman; 1 Photographic Prints; 13.3 X 8 cm (Object 056 Digital Copy Only)
    Mountains/Hills; Water; Landscapes; Jordan; Photographic Prints; Gelatin Silver Prints
  - Russian Orthodox Convent of the Acension, Jerusalem., Circa 1910s - 1930s; ref131; Fuleihan, Nasri Suleiman; 1 Photographic Prints; 8.5 X 11.3 cm (Object 056 Digital Copy Only)
    Religious Crosses; Orthodox Christianity; Jerusalem; Churches; Religious Sites; Photographic Prints; Gelatin Silver Prints; English Writing; Palestine
  - Wadi Mujib, Dead Sea., Circa 1910s - 1930s; ref132; Fuleihan, Nasri Suleiman; 1 Photographic Prints; 13.9X 8.3 cm (Object 056 Digital Copy Only)
    Gelatin Silver Prints; Photographic Prints; Ma'in, Jordan; Dead Sea; Water; English Writing; Rivers; Landscapes
  - Landscape of Nubian sandstone formation in Wadi Mujib, Dead Sea., Circa 1910s - 1930s; ref133; Fuleihan, Nasri Suleiman; 1 Photographic Prints; 8.4 X 13.8 cm (Object 056 Digital Copy Only)
    English Writing; Water; Dead Sea; Landscapes; Mountains/Hills; Photographic Prints; Gelatin Silver Prints; Ma'in, Jordan
  - Shore line of Lisan Peninsula, Dead Sea, Circa 1910s - 1930s; ref134; Fuleihan, Nasri Suleiman; 1 Photographic Prints; 8.4 X 14.6 cm (Object 056 Digital Copy Only)
    Water; Dead Sea; Landscapes; English Writing; Photographic Prints; Gelatin Silver Prints; Palestine; Jordan
  - A group portrait including Nasri Fuleihan (third from left) and other men., Circa 1910s - 1930s; ref135; Fuleihan, Nasri Suleiman; 1 Photographic Prints; 8.5 X 13.3 cm (Object 056 Digital Copy Only)
    Men; Hats; Canes/Walking Sticks; Fez/Tarboush; Regional/National Dress; Group Portraits; Photographic Prints; Gelatin Silver Prints; Palestine; Turbans
  - People walking in an alley, Jerusalem., Circa 1910s - 1930s; ref136; Fuleihan, Nasri Suleiman; 1 Photographic Prints; 11.5 X 8.5 cm (Object 056 Digital Copy Only)
    Streets/Roads; Boys; Children; Buildings; Jerusalem; Photographic Prints; Gelatin Silver Prints; Palestine; Group Portraits
  - Portrait of man on a horse in front of tents., Circa 1910s - 1930s; ref137; Fuleihan, Nasri Suleiman; 1 Photographic Prints; 8.2 X 14 cm (Object 056 Digital Copy Only)
    Men; Regional/National Dress; Individual Portraits; Photographic Prints; Horses; Animals; Gelatin Silver Prints; Tents; Palestine
  - Men on horses and camels on top of a hill., Circa 1910s - 1930s; ref138; Fuleihan, Nasri Suleiman; 1 Photographic Prints; 8.4 X 14 cm (Object 056 Digital Copy Only)
    Guns; Weapons; Hats; Canes/Walking Sticks; Horses; Animals; Regional/National Dress; Camels; Men; Group Portraits; Deserts; Palestine; Photographic Prints; Gelatin Silver Prints
  - Men on horses and camels in front of mountain range., Circa 1910s - 1930s; ref139; Fuleihan, Nasri Suleiman; 1 Photographic Prints; 8.4 X 13.9 cm (Object 056 Digital Copy Only)
    Camels; Horses; Hats; Men; Group Portraits; Animals; Mountains/Hills; Deserts; Palestine; Photographic Prints; Gelatin Silver Prints; Landscapes
  - A group portrait with one man with his back to the camera on the roof of Amdursky's Hotel., Circa 1910s - 1930s; ref140; Fuleihan, Nasri Suleiman; 1 Photographic Prints; 8.5 X 13.9 cm (Object 056 Digital Copy Only)
    Men; Regional/National Dress; Group Portraits; Children; Boys; Fez/Tarboush; Guns; Weapons; Swords/Knives; Facial Hair; Palestine; Photographic Prints; Gelatin Silver Prints; Hotels; Jerusalem; Hats
  - Interior of Zedekiah's Cave (Solomon's quarries), Jerusalem., Circa 1910s - 1930s; ref141; Fuleihan, Nasri Suleiman; 1 Photographic Prints; 7.9 X 9.2 cm (Object 056 Digital Copy Only)
    Gelatin Silver Prints; Photographic Prints; Caves; Quarry/Mine; Jerusalem; Religious Sites; Freemasonry; Archaeological Sites/Artifacts; English Writing; Palestine
  - A column and a statue in the Ashkelon/Ashqelon archeological site (linked ref 128, 143, 367 and 415)., Circa 1923 - 1930; ref142; Fuleihan, Nasri Suleiman; 1 Photographic Prints; 10.4 X 7.9 cm (Object 056 Digital Copy Only)
    Gelatin Silver Prints; Photographic Prints; Statues/Sculptures; Archaeological Sites/Artifacts; Outdoors; Palestine; Ashḳelon/Ashqelon
  - Nasri Fuleihan (center) and two men in the Ashkelon/Ashqelon archeological site. (linked ref 128, 142, 367 and 415)., Circa 1923 - 1930; ref143; Fuleihan, Nasri Suleiman; 1 Photographic Prints; 7.9 X 10.3 cm (Object 056 Digital Copy Only)
    Gelatin Silver Prints; Photographic Prints; Archaeological Sites/Artifacts; Statues/Sculptures; Men; Hats; Eye Glasses/Sunglasses; Smoking; Facial Hair; Bow Ties; Outdoors; Ashḳelon/Ashqelon; Tobacco pipes; Clocks/Watches; Palestine
  - Portrait of Raphael Clous(?) on a postcard sent to Nasri Fuleihan., 22 April 1916; ref144; R. Guilleminot, Bœspflug et Cie, Paris; 1 Photographic Prints; 13.8 X 8.5 cm (Object 056 Digital Copy Only)
    Photographic Prints; Facial Hair; Studio Photography; Individual Portraits; Men; French Writing; Unknown Locations; Handkerchiefs /Pocket Squares; Signatures
  - Entrance of Wadi Zarqa Ma'in, Dead Sea., Circa 1910s - 1930s; ref145; Fuleihan, Nasri Suleiman; 1 Photographic Prints; 15 X 8.4 cm (Object 056 Digital Copy Only)
    Gelatin Silver Prints; Photographic Prints; Dead Sea; Ma'in, Jordan; Mountains/Hills; Outdoors; English Writing
  - Wadi Zarqa Ma'in, Dead Sea., Circa 1910s - 1930s; ref146; Fuleihan, Nasri Suleiman; 1 Photographic Prints; 13.8 X 8.4 cm (Object 056 Digital Copy Only)
    Gelatin Silver Prints; Photographic Prints; Ma'in, Jordan; Rivers; Mountains/Hills; Dead Sea; Outdoors; English Writing; Landscapes
  - Hill of Masada, Dead Sea., Circa 1910s - 1930s; ref147; Fuleihan, Nasri Suleiman; 1 Photographic Prints; 8.3 X 13.8 cm (Object 056 Digital Copy Only)
    Gelatin Silver Prints; Photographic Prints; Dead Sea; Palestine; Mountains/Hills; Deserts; Outdoors; English Writing; Landscapes
  - Dead Sea deposits, Wadi Zarqa Ma'in Dead Sea., Circa 1910s - 1930s; ref148; Fuleihan, Nasri Suleiman; 1 Photographic Prints; 14.2 X 8.3 cm (Object 056 Digital Copy Only)
    Gelatin Silver Prints; Photographic Prints; Mountains/Hills; Ma'in, Jordan; Dead Sea; English Writing; Outdoors; Landscapes
  - Spring deposits near Hammamat Ma'in, Dead Sea., Circa 1910s - 1930s; ref149; Fuleihan, Nasri Suleiman; 1 Photographic Prints; 8.4 X 14.6 cm (Object 056 Digital Copy Only)
    Gelatin Silver Prints; Photographic Prints; Deserts; Dead Sea; Ma'in, Jordan; Outdoors; English Writing; Landscapes
  - Badland formations below Masada, Dead Sea., Circa 1910s - 1930s; ref150; Fuleihan, Nasri Suleiman; 1 Photographic Prints; 8.4 X 14.7 cm (Object 056 Digital Copy Only)
    Gelatin Silver Prints; Photographic Prints; Deserts; Ma'in, Jordan; Mountains/Hills; Outdoors; English Writing; Landscapes
  - People standing in the Church of St. John the Baptist, Sebastia., Circa 1910s - 1930s; ref151; Fuleihan, Nasri Suleiman; 1 Photographic Prints; 11.7 X 8.5 cm (Object 056 Digital Copy Only)
    Nablus; Children; Boys; Churches; Religious Sites; Archaeological Sites/Artifacts; Gelatin Silver Prints; Photographic Prints; English Writing; Palestine; Group Portraits
  - The east side of Jebel Usdum (Mount Sodom), Dead Sea., Circa 1910s - 1930s; ref152; Fuleihan, Nasri Suleiman; 1 Photographic Prints; 8.3 X 14 cm (Object 056 Digital Copy Only)
    Gelatin Silver Prints; Photographic Prints; Dead Sea; Mountains/Hills; Mount Sodom/Jebel Usdum, Newe Zohar; English Writing; Outdoors; Palestine; Landscapes
  - Overhanging cliffs of salt in the east side Jebel Usdum (Mount Sodom), Dead Sea., Circa 1910s - 1930s; ref153; Fuleihan, Nasri Suleiman; 1 Photographic Prints; 15 X 8.2 cm (Object 056 Digital Copy Only)
    Gelatin Silver Prints; Photographic Prints; Mount Sodom/Jebel Usdum, Newe Zohar; Dead Sea; Mountains/Hills; Beaches; English Writing; Palestine; Landscapes
  - A mountainous landscape., Circa 1910s - 1930s; ref154; Fuleihan, Nasri Suleiman; 1 Photographic Prints; 8.2 X 14 cm (Object 056 Digital Copy Only)
    Dead Sea; Gelatin Silver Prints; Photographic Prints; Mountains/Hills; Mount Sodom/Jebel Usdum, Newe Zohar; Landscapes; Outdoors; Palestine
  - A mountainous landscape., Circa 1910s - 1930s; ref155; Fuleihan, Nasri Suleiman; 1 Photographic Prints; 8.3 X 14 cm (Object 056 Digital Copy Only)
    Dead Sea; Mountains/Hills; Gelatin Silver Prints; Photographic Prints; Mount Sodom/Jebel Usdum, Newe Zohar; Landscapes; Outdoors; Deserts; Palestine
  - A mountainous landscape., Circa 1910s - 1930s; ref156; Fuleihan, Nasri Suleiman; 1 Photographic Prints; 8.3 X 14 cm (Object 056 Digital Copy Only)
    Mount Sodom/Jebel Usdum, Newe Zohar; Mountains/Hills; Dead Sea; Gelatin Silver Prints; Photographic Prints; Deserts; Landscapes; Outdoors; Palestine
  - Ruins of a stone building in Palestine or Jordan (linked ref159)., Circa 1910s - 1930s; ref157; Fuleihan, Nasri Suleiman; 1 Photographic Prints; 8.5 X 14 cm (Object 056 Digital Copy Only)
    Gelatin Silver Prints; Photographic Prints; Archaeological Sites/Artifacts; Mountains/Hills; Palestine; Jordan
  - Cliffs near Wadi Mujib., Circa 1910s - 1930s; ref158; Fuleihan, Nasri Suleiman; 1 Photographic Prints; 8.3 X 14.8 cm (Object 056 Digital Copy Only)
    Gelatin Silver Prints; Photographic Prints; Wadi al Mujib, Jordan; Dead Sea; Mountains/Hills; Outdoors; Landscapes
  - Ruins of a stone building in Palestine or Jordan (linked ref157)., Circa 1910s - 1930s; ref159; Fuleihan, Nasri Suleiman; 1 Photographic Prints; 8.4 X 13.9 cm (Object 056 Digital Copy Only)
    Gelatin Silver Prints; Photographic Prints; Archaeological Sites/Artifacts; Mountains/Hills; Landscapes; Palestine; Jordan
  - Portrait of a man wearing a suit., Circa 1910s - 1930s; ref160; Fuleihan, Nasri Suleiman; 1 Photographic Prints; 14 X 8.5 cm (Object 056 Digital Copy Only)
    Gelatin Silver Prints; Photographic Prints; Individual Portraits; Fez/Tarboush; Facial Hair; Outdoors; Hotels; Jerusalem; Palestine; Cigarettes; Smoking; Clocks/Watches; Men; Hats
  - A cliff edge in Palestine or Jordan, Circa 1910s - 1930s; ref161; Fuleihan, Nasri Suleiman; 1 Photographic Prints; 14 X 8.4 cm (Object 056 Digital Copy Only)
    Gelatin Silver Prints; Photographic Prints; Mountains/Hills; Outdoors; Palestine; Landscapes; Jordan
  - A mountainous landscape in Palestine or Jordan., Circa 1910s - 1930s; ref162; Fuleihan, Nasri Suleiman; 1 Photographic Prints; 8.5 X 14 cm (Object 056 Digital Copy Only)
    Photographic Prints; Gelatin Silver Prints; Mountains/Hills; Landscapes; Outdoors; Palestine; Jordan
  - A mountainous landscape in Palestine or Jordan., Circa 1910s - 1930s; ref163; Fuleihan, Nasri Suleiman; 1 Photographic Prints; 8.3 X 14 cm (Object 056 Digital Copy Only)
  - A mountainous landscape in Palestine or Jordan., Circa 1910s - 1930s; ref164; Fuleihan, Nasri Suleiman; 1 Photographic Prints; 8.2 X 14 cm (Object 056 Digital Copy Only)
  - A mountainous landscape in Palestine or Jordan., Circa 1910s - 1930s; ref165; Fuleihan, Nasri Suleiman; 1 Photographic Prints; 8.4 X 14 cm (Object 056 Digital Copy Only)
  - A mountainous landscape in Palestine or Jordan., Circa 1910s - 1930s; ref166; Fuleihan, Nasri Suleiman; 1 Photographic Prints; 14 X 8.3 cm (Object 056 Digital Copy Only)
    Photographic Prints; Mountains/Hills; Landscapes; Gelatin Silver Prints; Palestine; Jordan
  - Men on a boat with an Ottoman flag, Jaffa., Circa 1910s - 1930s; ref167; Fuleihan, Nasri Suleiman; 1 Photographic Prints; 11.3 X 8 cm (Object 056 Digital Copy Only)
    Photographic Prints; Gelatin Silver Prints; Jaffa; Mediterranean Sea; Boats/Ships; Men; Fez/Tarboush; Seas; English Writing; Outdoors; Flags; Regional/National Dress; Palestine; Group Portraits; Hats
  - Two clergymen in front of entrance to the Armenian Cathedral of Saint James, Jerusalem., Circa 1910s - 1930s; ref168; Fuleihan, Nasri Suleiman; 1 Photographic Prints; 11.4 X 8.5 cm (Object 056 Digital Copy Only)
    Photographic Prints; Gelatin Silver Prints; Religious Sites; Religious Imagery; Churches; Doors/Entrances; Lanterns/Lamps; Facial Hair; Priests/Clergymen; Palestine; Group Portraits; Men
  - Boats loaded with cargo with Jaffa port in the background., Circa 1910s - 1930s; ref169; Fuleihan, Nasri Suleiman; 1 Photographic Prints; 11.4 X 8.5 cm (Object 056 Digital Copy Only)
    Photographic Prints; Gelatin Silver Prints; Jaffa; Mediterranean Sea; Boats/Ships; Men; Outdoors; English Writing; Palestine; Transportation; Landscapes
  - Boats in front of Jaffa port., Circa 1910s - 1930s; ref170; Fuleihan, Nasri Suleiman; 1 Photographic Prints; 11.5 X 8.5 cm (Object 056 Digital Copy Only)
    Photographic Prints; Gelatin Silver Prints; Boats/Ships; Jaffa; Men; Fez/Tarboush; Docks/Piers/Jetties; Outdoors; Palestine; Transportation; Hats
  - Persian pilgrims awaiting Epiphany ceremony (from text on reverse)., Circa 1910s - 1930s; ref171; Fuleihan, Nasri Suleiman; 1 Photographic Prints; 11.3 X 8.6 cm (Object 056 Digital Copy Only)
    Photographic Prints; Gelatin Silver Prints; Baptisms; Boats/Ships; Jordan River; Religious Ceremony; Religious Sites; Men; Women; Children; English Writing; Outdoors; Jordan; Palestine; Pilgrims
  - A group of men standing on top of stone building (linked ref189)., Circa 1910s - 1930s; ref172; Fuleihan, Nasri Suleiman; 1 Photographic Prints; 8.3 X 13.3 cm (Object 056 Digital Copy Only)
    Photographic Prints; Gelatin Silver Prints; Men; Buildings; Regional/National Dress; Palestine; Group Portraits; Archaeological Sites/Artifacts; Turbans
  - A man and two boys at the House of Simon the Tanner, Jaffa., Circa 1910s - 1930s; ref173; Fuleihan, Nasri Suleiman; 1 Photographic Prints; 11.4 X 8.4 cm (Object 056 Digital Copy Only)